Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Case Files, 1922-1988
  - Kent, Rockwell v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Thesis of Mary Eileen Doyle; Passport), 1957-1963, 1965, 1967 (Box 12b, Folder 12)
  - Kenyatta, Muhammad, et al. v. Clarence Kelley, Undated (Box 12b, Folder 13)
  - Kinoy, Joanne and Arthur Kinov v. USA(I), 1975-1979 (Box 12b, Folder 14)
  - Kinoy v. USA(II), 1975-1979 (Box 12b, Folder 15)
  - Kipperman, Stephanie v. USA, 1976 (Box 12b, Folder 16)
  - Korry, Edward v. International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation and Harold S. Geneen, 1977 (Box 12b, Folder 17)
  - Krause, Arthur v. James Rhodes, et al.(Kent State), 1976-1979 (Box 12b, Folder 18)
  - Levy Howard B. v. Jacob J. Parker: Formal File(I), Undated (Box 12b, Folder 19)
  - Levy v. Parker: Formal File(II), Undated (Box 12b, Folder 20)
  - Lykken, David v. Edward Vaureck(I), 1970s (Box 12b, Folder 21)
  - Lykken v. Vaureck(II), 1970s (Box 12b, Folder 22)
  - MacEwan, Alan and Mary MacEwan v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Passport), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Maxfield, Ruth Helena v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Passport), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - McGuire, Ronald, et al. v. Board of Higher Education of NYC(City College Demonstration: Students for Democratic Society): Briefs, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: City College Suspension, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: Disciplinary Proceedings Conducted at City College, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: Formal, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: General, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: Interviews; Notes Statements of Arrestees, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NYC: Photos; Press Coverage, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - McGuire v. Board of Higher Education of NY C: Students for a Democratic Society Memos, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - McSurely, Alan v. John McClellan, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, Parren J. v. Elliot Richardson, Undated, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mottola, Gary v. Richard Nixon, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Nathan, Otto v. John Sachel: Correspondence (The Papers of Albert Einstein; Princeton University Press), 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: Correspondence (Background Material Estate and Princeton), 1950-1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: General Files, 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: General Files, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: General Files, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: General Files, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: Memorandum, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: Nathan's Summaries (I), Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: Nathan's Summaries (II), Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nathan v. Sachel: Nathan's Summaries (III), Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees Suit, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - New York, People of the State of v. Cheng, Tzutsai (Immigration)(I), 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New York v. Cheng(II), 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - New York v. Cheng(III), 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - New York v. Cheng, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New York v. Cheng: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - New York v. Cheng: English Court Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - New York v. Cheng: Formal, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - New York v. Cheng: Reference Letters, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - New York v. Cheng: Research; Witness Statements, Undated, 1962-1972, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - New York, People of the State of v. Robert Dunn(Bail Fund of the Civil Rights Congress of New York), 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - New York, People of the State of v. Isaac Fergusson and Charles Ruthenberg, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Richard v. Ernest A. Fitzgerald(Research), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Nyden, Paul J. v. University of Pittsburgh: Briefs, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Correspondence and Exhibits, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Dr. Sharon L. Johnson, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Preliminary Injunction, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Press Coverage, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Report of Reviewing Committee, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Reports, Notes, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Research, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Nyden v. University of Pittsburgh: Summary of Case, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Ollman, Bertell v. John S. Toll, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Paton, Lori, et al. v. LaPrade, J. Wallace, et al.(I), 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Paton v. LaPrade(II), 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Peck, James v. F.B.I. Director, Clarence M. Kelley(USA): Chronology of Events, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Correspondence - Copeland, Edward, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Court Documents - Docket Sheets, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3a)
  - Peck v. USA: Depositions - Background Material, 1960s (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Bergman, Walter, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Doar, John, 1961, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Jenkins, Thomas J. (I), 1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Jenkins, Thomas, J. (II), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Jenkins, Thomas, J. (III), 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Jenkins, Thomas J., Documents, 1960s, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Jenkins, Exhibits, 1961, 1979 (?) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Kemp, Barrett, 1961, 1979, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Lynne, Seymour H., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Depositions, Markings, 1979, 1980s (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Marshall, Burke, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - McGowan, Clement L. Jr., 1,961, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Depositions - Miscellaneous Documents from Depositions, 1960s (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Peck, James, 1961, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Rowe, Gary T. Jr. (I), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Rowe, Gary T. Jr. (II), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Rowe, Gary T. Jr. (III), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Rowe, Background, 1960s, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Rowe, Exhibits 4-51, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - Smith, Howard, 1961, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Deposition - White, Justice Byron R., 1960s, 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Discovery, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Discovery, #31, 1961, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Discovery - Documents, Illegible (I), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Discovery - Documents, Illegible (II), 1961 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Docs Not Previously Produced, Vol. II, 1979 (?) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Document List, 1970s-1980s (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents: Notes, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Bergman v. Kelley, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Cook, Thomas, 1950s, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Doar Produced, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - FBI File: Peck, James, 1940s, 1958, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - FBI Handbook, 1961, 1975-1977, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - McFall, Byron Edwards, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Raby, Kenneth N., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Rosen, Alex, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Rowe, Gary, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Rowe, Gary (I), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Peck v. USA: Documents - Rowe, Gary (II), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Documents Produced: 137-6295-2, 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit List, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits Missing - List, 1980s (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 1-22, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 23 (I), 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 23 (II), 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 23 (III), 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 24-68, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 69-83, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 84-110, 1960-1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 111-147, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 150-185, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 186 (I), 1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 186 (II), 1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 187-196, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 197 (I), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibit 197 (II), 1961 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 198-222, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 223-241, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Exhibits 242-257, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Government Witness List, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Peck v. USA: Index of Peck Files, Undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Peck v. USA: Memos, Notes, 1976-1983 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Documents Produced, 1961, 1962, 1969-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit List, ca.1980s (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits Offered But Not Received, 1961-1966 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1 Vol. 1, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 3, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 4, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 5, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 6, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 7, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 8, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 9, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 10, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 11, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 1, Vol. 12, 1960s, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 1, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 3, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 4, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 5, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 6, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 7 & 8, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 9, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 10, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 11, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 2, Vol. 12, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 3, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 1, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 3, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 4, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 5, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 6, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 7, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 4, Vol. 8, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 5, Vol. 1, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 5, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 5, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 6, Vol. 1, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 6, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 6, Vol. 3, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 7, 1961, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 8, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 9, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 10, Vol. 1, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 10, Vol. 2, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 10, Vol. 3, 1960s (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 11-16, Undated, 1961, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 18-19, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 19a, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 22a-22c, 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 22d, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 25, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 26a, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 26b, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 26c, 1960s (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 27, 1960s, 1970s (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 29-33, 1961, 1975, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 41, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 41 (2), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 42-67, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 101-124, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 125-144, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 145-195, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 201-225, Undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 226-250, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 251-287, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 289-352, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 354-372; 374-387, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit 373, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 388-426, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 427-439, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 1001-1070, 1960s-1970s (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 1071-1088, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits 1089-1102, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit To Reoffer, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibit Unknown Number, 1960s (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits - Photographs (I), 1961 (Box 27a, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Plaintiffs Exhibits - Photographs (II), 1961 (Box 27a, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Press, 1960s-1980s (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (I), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (II), 1960s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI), 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (I), 1961 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (II), 1961 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (III), 1961 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (IV), 1961 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI), May 1961-May 23, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (I), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Records (FBI) (II), May 1905 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Research, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Alabama Racial Violence (Pamphlets), 1960s (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Bergman Staff Report, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Bergman v. Kelly, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Bergman v. Kemp, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Bergman v. USA, et al., 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Conspiracy, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Thomas Cook and Gary Rowe, Undated, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Research CORE, 1960s, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Informer, Undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Research JFK Library, 1961, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Legal, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Liuzzo, et al. v. USA, 1960s, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Liuzzo, et al. v. USA, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Liuzzo, et al. v. USA, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Liuzzo, et al. v. USA Transcripts (I), Undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Liuzzo, et al. v. USA Transcripts (II), Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Press in 1960s (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Gary Rowe, 1978-1980, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Peck v. USA: Research USA v. Llewelyn, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Peck v. USA: Research USA v. US KKK, et al., 1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Peck v. USA: Research Wilkins Case, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Peck v. USA: Settlement and Appeal, 1981-1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript Excerpted Indices, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript Index, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Oct 5, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jun 19, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jun 19, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 8, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, May 1, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 5, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 17, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 18, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 20, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 24, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 25, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 26, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 27, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Jan 28, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Feb 7, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript, Mar 11, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Peck v. USA: Transcript Conference, Mar 24, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Nelson, Steve: Correspondence, May 5, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania v. Nelson: Correspondence, May 6, 1905-1954 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania v. Nelson: Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania v. Nelson: Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania v. Nelson: General, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Soul, David: Briefs (I), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Briefs (II), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Rev. Daniel N. Solberg, 1983-1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Exhibits - Video Cassettes (2); Audio Cassette, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Formal, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Formal, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Memos, Press, Notes, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Miscellaneous, Undated, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Superior Court of Pennsylvania Reproduced Record, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Superior Court of Pennsylvania, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania v. Soul: Supreme Court of Pennsylvania Formal, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Philadelphia Resistance, et al. v. Mitchell, John, et al., 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Price, William v. Kearney, John et al.: Briefs (FBI case), 1980 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Price v. Kearney: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Price v. Kearney: Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Price v. Kearney: Formal File, 1972-1980 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Price v. Kearney: Related Cases - Judith Clark, et al. v. USA, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Price v. Kearney: Related Cases - Lewis Cole, Gray, Blackburn, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Price v. Kearney: William Addison Price FOIA, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Rabinowtiz, Joni v. Hon. Bootle: Formal File, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Riverside Church v. National Black Economic Development Conference(NBEDC): Briefs, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Riverside Church v. NBEDC: Christian Anti-Defamation League, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Riverside Church v. NBEDC: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Riverside Church v. NBEDC: Formal File, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Riverside Church v. NBEDC: Miscellaneous, 1954-1969 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Riverside Church v. NBEDC: Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Riverside Church v. NBEDC: Supreme Court, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Robertson, Fern v. USA, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)